http://independentequineagents.com/privacy-notice/

Independent Equine Agents Privacy Notice
Independent Equine Agents would like to make you aware of privacy practices for www.independentequineagents.com . It is our goal to make users aware of how we protect the confidentiality of the personal information collected by this website.
INFORMATION COLLECTED AND USE
Independent Equine Agents is the sole owner of the non-public personal information that we collect on this site. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or direct contact from you. Personal information we collect includes that contained on applications or other forms that you submit to us, such as name, address, and social security number.
Your information will be used in response to the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than those necessary to fulfill your enquiry of business.
SECURITY
Only employees of Independent Equine Agents and those affiliated who need the information to service your account have access to your personal information. Information you submit via the website is protected both online and offline.
Sensitive information (such as credit card data) is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. Please note the ‘closed lock’ icon at the bottom of your web browser.
CONTACTING US
Should you have questions or concerns about this privacy notice or if you are interested in learning more on how we protect your information please contact our staff. We can provide you with additional information on our practices upon request.
